Southwest Folklore Center Cassette Recordings Collection, 1975-1995
University of Arizona Libraries, Special Collections
- Cisco Band, volume two: Papago chicken scratch, The Cisco Band, 1981; Phoenix, AZ., Canyon Records, p1981; 1 sound cassette, analog; NOTES: Photograph of The Cisco Band on cover... Musicians: Francis Enriquez, saxophone and guitar; Frank Joaquin, guitar and saxophone; John Lewis, Jr., bass and accordian; David Narcho, drums; Benny Martinez, accordion; Damon Enriquez, percussion... Chicken's itch -- Around here chote -- Mi rancerito polka -- Awhite back chote -- Silva cumbia -- El Romance chote -- Early Sunday morning polka -- Remembering mazurka -- Herb's tune polka -- Ebanito chote -- Mula Broncho polka -- Las Panchitas chote --; SWF 87.14/C.108
- Jose's and Gomez Band: Papago chicken scratch, Jose's and Gomez Band, 1985; Phoenix, AZ., Canyon Records, p1985; 1 sound cassette, analog; NOTES: Photograph of Jose's and Gomez Band on cover... Musicians include: Alex Gomez, saxophone; Joe Henry Jose, accordian, saxophone, organ; Tim Gomez, drums; Clifford Jose, guitar; Nick Jose, bass... O'odham Ha-Kaidag waila ("Papago Sound") --Sifoidak chote ("Bitter Fields Song") -- G-Añ hu bab ke:k waila ("I'm there") -- Coyote howl chote -- Morning star waila -- Kuawaliya (square dance) -- Carpenter waila -- De-No's waltz (Ma:sulga) -- Kohatk village waila -- Pako'ola Ne-ei chote (pascola) -- Waw Giwulk waila ("Baboquivari mountain") -- Up and down cumbia --; SWF 87.14/C.109
- Baxter Black and Friends: Red, Woody, Bob, Ed, Roger, Doug, Michael, Hoyt, Hodley, Walt, Too Slim, and Carlos, Black, Baxter, 1984; Denver, CO., Coyote Cowboy Company, copyright by Baxter Black, 1984; 1 sound cassette, analog; NOTES: Photograph of Baxter Black and a dog on cover... All poems written by Baxter Black... People are funny critters -- The New hat (Red Steagall) -- Jekyll and Hide Cattle Company -- Sermon on the can (Walt Garrison) -- Supersalesman -- The Silent partner (Reba McEntire appears courtesy of MCA Records) -- Camp cookie (Too Slim LaBour) -- Cowboy's goin' Hollywood (Ranger Doug Crenn) -- The Gay caballero -- The Old days (Michael McGinnis) -- The Cowboy and the lady -- The Sandhills senior (Holly Barrett) -- The Big high and lonesome (Carlos Ashley) --; SWF 87.15/C.1
- Baxter Black live, Black, Baxter, 1984; Denver, CO., Coyote Cowboy Company, copyright by Baxter Black, 1984; 1 sound cassette, analog; NOTES: Photograph of Baxter Black on cover... Music by "Tumbleweeds"... Cindy Lou Black, fiddle; Rick and Sherry Suhr, back-up vocals... All songs and poems written and performed by Baxter Black... The Horse -- The Cow committee -- One more year -- Cow savvy -- Five flat -- Sellin' Prewitt's sow -- I ain't no cowboy -- Last of the singin' cowboys -- Runnin' out of sunsets -- Colorado cowboy -- Take care of yer friends -- The Vegetarian's nightmare --; SWF 87.15/C.2
- The Titan Valley Warheads, Titan Valley Warheads, Tucson, AZ., The Sound Factory; 1 sound cassette, analog; NOTES: Cover art and design by Ned Sutton... Musicians: Gary Kuitert, mandolin, vocals; Bob Dennoncourt, bass, vocals; John Mattingley, guitar, vocals; Ross Nickerson, banjo; Don Johnson, fiddle, vocals... Jumping the frog (D. Johnson) -- Two liitle boys (P.D.) -- Adobe hacienda (P.D.) -- Don't stop now (R. Nickerson) -- You can have her (W. Cook) -- Traveling kind (S. Young) -- Brown Mountain light (S. Weisman) -- Remington rider (Penny/Remington) -- Homegrown tomatoes (G. Clark) -- Maiden's prayer (B. Wills) -- Might dark to travel (B. Monroe) --; SWF 88.1/C.1
- Algo hermoso para Cristo, 1 sound cassette, analog; NOTES: Illustration on cover by Mario... From Acquisitions Inventory: "this tape was a fund raiser for the local Cursillo movement and features local and regional Cursillo singing groups"... In Spanish and English... Algo hermoso para Dios (Kenny) -- Mas alta de sol (Mariachi de Colores) -- El Alfarero (Casa Grande) -- I have decided to follow Jesus (Tohono O'odham group) -- Quien nos apartará de amor de Cristo (Safford) -- Much Amor (Yuma) -- El Pescador (Mamuth) -- Donde nace la flor (Kernny) -- Christo cuento conmigo (Mariachi de Colores) -- Dios y Lombre (Casa Grande) -- This is the day (Tohono O'odham group) -- Christo rey (Yuma) -- La Agonia de Christo (Safford) -- Entre tus manos (Mamuth) -- De colores (Diosesi de Tucson) --; SWF 88.2/C.1
- Memorable songs of the old time: Navajo two step and skip dance songs, Chinle Valley Singers, 1987; Phoenix, AZ., Canyon Records, p1987; 1 sound cassette, analog, vol.2; NOTES: Photograph of Chinle Valley Singers on cover... Singers inlcude: Linda Teller, Anita Davis, Elizabeth Davis, Elsi Davis Deswood.. Two step dance songs: Stay with me -- Is my partner present? -- Don't bother the China girl -- Good friendship -- My worriness -- You dance beautifully -- Skip dance songs: Who are you here for? -- Billy goat song -- It's difficult but let's be together -- You broke my heart -- I followed you to see what it's like -- Young man, who are you here for? --; SWF 88.5/C.1
- Tsi'Yi'Tóhi' Singers (Woodspring): Navajo skip and two step dance songs, Tsi'Yi'Tóhi' Singers, 1987; Phoenix, AZ., Canyon Records, p1987; 1 sound cassette, analog; NOTES: Photograph of Tsi'Yi'Tóhi' Singers on cover... Singers include: Mary Dedman; Ann Dobey; Paul Dobey, lead singer and drummer; Bera Shirley; Miller Dedman, Jr.; Erin Dobey... Skip dance songs: Gamerco girl -- Indifference -- Navajo-Hopi tribe unity -- That girl -- I wish you follow -- Beautiful Blackfoot girl -- People's happiness -- Polacco -- Two-step dance songs: Get away -- Flagstaff girl -- Young generation -- Dancing partner used to say -- Gifted with valuables -- Meet me in Gallup -- Always stood by the road -- Hopi girl --; SWF 88.5/C.2
- Joe Miguel and the Blood Brothers: Chicken scratch, Miguel, Joe and The Blood Brothers, 1987; Phoenix, AZ., Canyon Records, p1987; 1 sound cassette, analog, vol.3; NOTES: Photograph of Joe Miguel and the Blood Brothers on cover... Musicians include: Joe Miguel, saxophone; Ronnie Joaquin, guitar and bass; Jose Velasco, Jr., drums; Tyson Whitman, accordion; Jesse Puentes, Jr., bass and guitar; Raymond Boley, executive producer... Sun tracks waila -- Dusty moccasin chote -- Buscando amores cumbia -- Many returns waila -- Injun vodka chote -- La Mucaro cumbia -- Night after night waila -- Sunrise chote -- Comanchos cumbia -- Nick's special waltz -- Lo Mucho que te quiero bolero -- Limbo cumbia --; SWF 88.5/C.3
- Thee/Express: Chicken scratch, Thee/Express, 1987; Phoenix, AZ., Canyon Records, p1987; 1 sound cassette, analog; NOTES: Photograph of Thee/Express on cover... Musicians include: Ricardo Vavages, accordian and bass; Rupert Vavages, acccordian and guitar; Isaac Vavages, saxophone; Lornzo Vavages, drums; Lucius Vavages, drums and percussion; Ronnie Juan, bass and accordion... 'Til mañama wao:a -- Sycamore co:di -- Ole Smokey waila -- Old style Masul'ga -- Alias waila -- Sabian cumbia -- Puss in the hat waila -- Jacked rabbit co:di -- RSV waila -- Greasewood co:di -- Arabian cubia -- Thee fox trot Paco'ola --; SWF 88.5/C.4
- Tohono O'odham Braves: Chicken scratch, Tohono O'odham Braves, 1987; Phoenix, AZ., Canyon Records, p1987; 1 sound cassette, analog; NOTES: Photograph of the Tohono O'odham Braves on cover... Musicians: Jason M. Wood, guitar and saxophone; Donnie B. Manuel, drums; Gilbert L. Jose, saxophone and bass; alex A. Cruz, bass and guitar; Marvin Jones, percussion... Braves special waila -- Komelik two-step -- Thono cumbia -- Weensy spider waila -- Limbo rock -- O'odham chote -- Wild flower waila -- Rocky top chote -- A.I.M. cumbia -- Farmer in the dell waila -- Braves cumbia -- Piasth tune waila --; SWF 88.5/C.5
- Lalo Mata y sus Llaneros, Mata, Lalo, Phoenix, AZ., Pantera Records Co.; 1 sound cassette, analog; NOTES: From Acqusitions Inventory: "Lalo Mata y sus Llaneros performed as the house band at La Cita Ballroom"... Gosare tus renuerdos -- La Carcel -- Desesperansa -- Motibos -- Las dos las gueria pa nic -- Cada vez -- Por el bien de los dos -- Lamberto guintero -- Pequena y frajel -- Cuarto vidas --; SWF 88.6/C.1
- Lalo Mata, Mata, Lalo, XLT Productions; 1 sound cassette, analog; NOTES: From Acquisitions Inventory: "Lalo Mata y sus Llaneros performed as the house band at La Cita Ballroom"... Todo paso (2:22) -- Vino maldito (2:10) -- Vestido blanco (2:23) -- Crieste (2:54) -- Vengan copas (2:11) -- Nesecito una companero (2:57) -- Marez cumbia (2:20) -- Anelo (2:46) -- Querido amigo (2:10) -- Francisoc Zarabia (2:20) --; SWF 88.6/C.2
- Corridos de la Revolution, 1988 February 2; Tucson, AZ., El Pueblo Neighborhood Center, February 2, 1988; 1 sound cassette, analog; NOTES; From acquisition file, "Talks by Raquel Goldsmith and Celeistino Fernández -- 3 songs by Francisco Gonzáles -- Corrido by Guillermo Suenz -- Corridos by Antonio Federico wth el group Christo Rey" --; SWF 88.10/C.1
- [Recordings of the St. Johns, Arizona, Mandolin and Guitar Society], St. Johns Mandolin and Guitar Club, 1962 August 15; Seattle, WA., Seattle World's Fair, August 15, 1962; 1 sound cassette, analog; Introduction -- Mocking bird hill -- Daisy Dee -- Napannec -- Vaya con Dios -- Dear hearts and gentle people --; SWF 88.14/C.1
- Interview with Leonardo Yañez, Yañez, Leonardo, 1988 June 23; Douglas, AZ., June 23, 1988; 1 sound cassette, analog; NOTES: Information from acquisitions file: Interview by James S. Griffith with Leonardo Yañez, corridos composer, about corridos and the famous race horses "Relampago" and "Moro de Cumpas"... Transcription located in acquisitions file...; SWF 88.15/C.1.T
- Gu-Achi Fiddlers: Old time O'odham fiddlers music, The Gu-Achi Fiddlers, 1988; Phoenix, AZ., Canyon Records, p1988; 1 sound cassette, analog; NOTES: On cover, photograph of the Gu-Achi Fiddlers... Notes on inside cover written by James S. Griffith about the history of Tohono O'odham fiddle music and biographical information about the Gu-Achi Fiddlers... Performers include: Gerald Leos, snare; Lester Vavages, fiddle; Tommy Lopez, bass drum; Wilfred Mendoza, guitar; Elliott Johnson, fiddle... Ali Oidah polka -- Bareterro teo-step -- Black Mountain mazurka -- Blackie polka -- Libby bird song mazurka -- Memories in Ajo polka -- Pinto beans two-step -- E.J. special polka -- Cababie two-step -- Down mazurka --; SWF 88.16/C.1
- Singin' Sam's Saddlebag of songs and Singin' Sam and friends, Singin' Sam Agins, West Sedona, AZ., Haywire Record Co.; 1 sound cassette, analog, stereo; NOTES: Label on container: "From the master tapes of two Singin' Sam Classic Cowboy albums"...Singin' Sam's Saddlebag of Songs: Lil' Joe the wrangler -- Old Chilsholm trail -- Sirree peaks -- City boarders -- Punchin' the dough -- 10,000 years ago -- Hair trigger newt -- Rawhide rope -- Jake and Roany -- Strawberry roan -- Tennis in Venice -- Red River Valley -- Singin' Sam and Friends: Philadelphia lawyer -- Peon named Pancho -- Had but fifty cents -- Dearly beloved -- Good old mountain dew -- Silver haired Daddy -- Cowboy Nick -- South coast -- Goin' back -- Yavapai Pete -- Cat came back -- Red Elk --; SWF 88.18/C.1
- Horse Tracks: Who shot the mules?, Knox, Ross and Steve Rafters, 1988; Prescott, AZ., Cave Productions, Cave Music Group, p1988; 1 sound cassette (42:84 minutes), analog; NOTES: Photograph of Ross Knox and Steve Rafters on cover...Musicians include: Ross Knox, peoms; Steve Rafters, vocals and guitar; Jeff Robertson, guitar; John Kennedy, fiddle and mandolin; Sondra Asa, banjo; Warren Miller, mandolin; Lou Steiger, harmonica...From cover: "A collection of original and traditional songs and poems of the working cowboy"...Easy chairs and saddle sores (3:00) -- The Moonshine Steer (2:53) -- Forgotten (1:53) -- Little Joe the wrangler -- Bear hunters bold (6:50) -- Old Paint (3:11) -- The Dude Wrangler (4:54) -- Droop ears (4:03) -- Cowboy at college (2:05) -- Little Joe the wrangler's sister Nell (4:03) -- The Old night hawk (5:52) --; SWF 88.19/C.1
- 1985 Arizona state fiddle champion: David Sharp, Shroup, David, Tempe, AZ., Cirillo Studios, p1985; 1 sound cassette, analog; NOTES: Photograph of David Shroup on cover...Sally Goodin -- Misty moonlight waltz -- Calgary polka -- Hell among the yearlings -- Skater's waltz -- Herman's rag -- Red wing -- Turkey in the straw -- Grey Eagle -- Arkansas traveler -- Cattle in the cane -- Tennessee waltz -- Dill pickles -- Tugboat -- Kentucky waltz -- Don't let the deal go down -- Ragtime Annie -- Leather britches -- Faded love -- Orange Blossom Special --; SWF 89.11/C.1
- AOTFA - Valley Chapter, AOTFA - Valley Chapter (Arizona Old Time Fiddlers' Association), 1989 January 8; Mesa, AZ., Recorded live at the Venture Out, January 8, 1989; 1 sound cassette, analog; NOTES: Photograph of Valley chapter musicians on cover...Performers listed on cover...Ragtime Annie -- Redwing -- Step it fast -- Darktown strutter's ball -- Abbotsford waltz -- Sweet Georgia Brown -- San Antonio Rose -- Down yonder -- Faded love -- South -- Ghost riders in the sky -- I'm confessin' -- Maiden's prayer -- Orange Blossom Special -- Golden slippers -- Jessie polka -- Wreck of the old 97 -- Darling Nellie Gray -- Huggies on highway -- John Ryan -- Mickey chewing bubble gum -- Black Mountain rag -- El rancho grande -- Canadian cotton eyed Joe -- Amarillo by morning -- Sally Goodin -- Old Joe Clark -- Blackberry blossom -- Eighth of January --; SWF 89.12/C.1
- Southpaw Shroup, Shroup, David, 1988; Phoenix, AZ., p1988; 1 sound cassette, analog; NOTES: Dedication: "This tape is dedicated to Carl E. Reiter, Master Violin Maker, Prescott, AZ."...More information on cover...Musicians: David Shroup, fiddle and harmonies; Mike Cirillo, accompaniment..."Special thanks to Peter Rolland for various arrangements"...Boil the cabbage down -- I'm confessing -- Liberty -- West Fork girls -- Maiden's prayer -- Jessie polka -- Silver bells -- Amazing grace -- Old rugged cross -- Golden slippers -- Tennessee waltz -- Buffalo gals -- Forty years ago waltz -- Soldier's joy -- Westphalia waltz -- Irish washerwoman's jig -- Cotton eyed Joe -- Fowl medley --; SWF 89.13/C.1
- The Zopes, The Zopes (Los Zopilotes), 198?; Tucson, AZ., Skin and Bones Music, [198?]; 1 sound cassette, analog; NOTES: Musicians: Dave Meko; Barry Richards; Bob Collier...Santa Cruz polka -- Rueben and Mercedes -- Papago gas -- Conchos -- Dragoon waltz -- La Gordita -- Bayou waltz -- Speedway mazurka -- Cumbia borachita --; SWF 89.15/C.1
- Pigs ate my speakers, Hector and the Javelinas, 1988; [Tucson, AZ.], Skin and Bones Music, Big Zeke Music, Prickly Pear Productions, p1988; 1 sound cassette, analog; NOTES: Musicians: Dave Meko, accordian and vocals; Rick Huston, guitars and vocals; Barry Richards, bass and vocals...Put your teeth back in -- Speedway mazurka -- Mr. D.J. -- Polka borachita -- Moses Ruben and Mercedes -- Joe's Cafe -- Squeezebox romancer -- Eddie --; SWF 89.15/C.2
- Signature album, Taylor, Sam, 1989; Aradia Music, Inc., Produced by Sam Taylor for Aradia Music, Inc., Assoc. Producer Gary Ford, August West Productions, p1989; 1 sound cassette, analog; NOTES: On cover, photograph of Sam Taylor, by Gary Ford...Dedication: "Dedicated to the Mother of my children"...Ice water -- Shop around -- You got the nerve -- Mother blues -- Rock yo ase ofe -- Good to ya -- Freak for pain -- Mother of the year -- Call the police -- Spirit -- Do you like it --; SWF 89.18/C.1
- The Paradox Bluegrass Band, The Paradox Bluegrass Band, 1985; Mesa, AZ., Peter Rolland, p1985; 1 sound cassette (60 minutes), analog, stereo; NOTES: From cover, "Recorded live in concert; August 31, 1985"...Performers include: Peter Rolland, fiddle, mandolin, lead vocals; Gail Rolland, bass; Jack Levy, guitar; Martin Sinclair, banjo...Cluck old hen -- Uncle Pen -- Hair trigger newt -- Over the rainbow -- Battle of New Orleans -- Pig in a pen -- Arkansas traveler -- Fisher's hornpipe -- Forked deer -- Bill Cheatum -- Listen to the mockingbird -- Foggy mountain breakdown -- John Henry -- Old Joe Clark/June apple -- Travlin' the high way home -- Leather britches -- Who broke the lock -- The Orange Blossom Special --; SWF 89.22/C.1
- Traditional American old time fiddling, Rolland, Peter and Gail Rolland, 1982; Kerr Cultural Center, [Produced by Peter Rolland], p1982; 1 sound cassette (60 minutes), analog, stereo; Tommy don't go -- Three legged milkstool -- Pigtown fling/Uncle Joe -- Last of Callahan/Cumberland Gap -- Bonapart's retreat -- Cripple Creek -- Yew Piney Mountain -- Brimmer's reel -- Humphrey's jig -- Jigset: Haste to the wedding/Irish washerwoman/Connaugtman's rambles -- Fowl medley: Turkey in the straw/Chicken reel/Cackling hen/Cluck old hen -- Wake up Susan -- Borga wiggle rag -- Turkey knob -- Lonestar rag -- Rutland's reel -- Lost Indian -- Black mountain blues -- Festival waltz -- Listen to the mockingbird -- Drowsy Maggie/The Black eyed lassie --; SWF 89.22/C.2
- The Cowboy Fiddle Band "Live", The Cowboy Fiddle Band, 1985; Mesa, AZ., Peter Rolland, p1985; 1 sound cassette (60 min.), analog, stereo; NOTES: From cover, "Live in concert at the Kern Cultural Center, December 7, 1984"... Performers include: Joe Baer, lead vocals, rhythm guitar; Marshall Raconsky, lead guitar; Bill Roberts - "Arkansas Willy"; Gail Rolland, upright bass; David Shoup, harmony vocals, melody fiddle; Julianna Waller, harmony fiddle; Peter Rolland, emcee, harmony and lead vocals, harmony fiddle, mandolin, all arrangements, management and production; Steve Kelsy, recording... Rose of San Antonio (Bob Wills) -- Maiden's prayer -- Corina, Corina -- South (B. Moten and T. Hayes) -- Bill Cheatum -- Rose of Avignmore -- Calgary polka -- Willie wants to fiddle too -- Faded love/Arkansas traveler (Bob Wills) -- Hair trigger newt -- Jessie polka -- Devil's dream -- Room full of roses (Tim Soencer) -- Tumbling tumbleweeds (Bob Nolan) -- East Tennessee blues -- Cool water (Bob Nolan) -- Romeo's last chance jog -- Willie's list: People I can whop --Jumbalaya (Hank Williams) -- The Tennessee waltz (Redd Stewart and Pee Wee King) -- The Orange Blossom Special --; SWF 89.22/C.3
- Los Piratas del Valle, Los Piratas del Valle, Phoenix, AZ., Pajarito Records and Recording Studio; 1 sound cassette, analog, stereo; NOTES: Photograph of Los Piratas del Valle on cover...From acquisition file, 89.25/C.1: La cuna vacia -- Me estoy acostumbrando -- Extranos -- Los ojos de mi morena -- La Noria escondída -- Amor a lo ligero -- El serenatero -- Me toco la de Derder -- Estrellas de plata -- Mi Lupita --; SWF 89.25/C.1
- Mariachi show, Los 4 Del Colonial, 198?; XLT Production, Marca Miramontes, [198?]; 1 sound cassette, analog; NOTES: From acquistion file, tape acquired in Phoenix, Arizona in 1986 or 1987... Burrito de Belen -- Blanca Navidad -- El Niño de Tambor -- Los Camparias -- Comido de Año Nuevo -- Feliz Navidad -- Noche de Paz -- Rudolfo el Reno -- Campanitas de Navidad -- Potpourri Nanideno; SWF 89.25/C.2
- [Interview with Ray Boley] tape 1, Boley, Ray [Raymond], 1989 December 13; Phoenix, AZ., December 13, 1989; 1 sound cassette, analog; NOTES: From acquisition file: Interview by James S. Griffith with Ray Boley, at Mr. Boley's home in Phoenix, Arizona. Mr. Boley is the founder and owner of Canyon Record Company..."the world's largest firm releasing Native American Music commercially"... Interview is about Mr. Boley's life, focusing on Canyon Record Company... Typed transcription of tape available in file, 89.26/C.1, 2...; SWF 89.26/C.1
- [Interview with Ray Boley] tape 2, Boley, Ray [Raymond], 1989 December 13; Phoenix, AZ., December 13, 1989; 1 sound cassette, analog; NOTES: From acquisition file: Interview by James S. Griffith with Ray Boley, at Mr. Boley's home in Phoenix, Arizona. Mr. Boley is the founder and owner of Canyon Record Company..."the world's largest firm releasing Native American Music commercially"... Interview is about Mr. Boley's life, focusing on Canyon Record Company... Typed transcription of tape available in file, 89.26/C.1, 2...; SWF 89.26/C.2
- [Glenn Ohrlin at Sharlot Hall Museum, tape 1], Ohrlin, Glenn, 1985 March 6; Prescott, AZ., Sharlot Hall Museum, March 6, 1985; 1 sound cassette, analog; NOTES: Performers include: Glenn Ohrlin; Gail Gardner; Earl Rogers; Everett Brisindine... From Acquistions Inventory, "contains stories, songs, and poems"...; SWF 89.27/C.1
- Glenn Ohrlin at Sharlot Hall Museum, tape 2, Ohrlin, Glenn, 1985 March 6; Prescott, AZ., Sharlot Hall Museum, [March 6, 1985?]; 1 sound cassette, analog; NOTES: From Acquisition Inventory, "Individuals recorded are Glenn Ohrlin, Gail Gardner, Earl Rogers and Everett Brisindine... contains stories, songs, and poems"...; SWF 89.27/C.2
- Glenn Ohrlin at Sharlot Hall Museum, tape 3, Ohrlin, Glenn, 1985 March 6; Prescott, AZ., Sharlot Hall Museum, [March 6, 1985?]; 1 sound cassette, analog; NOTES: From Acquisition Inventory, "Individuals recorded are Glenn Ohrlin, Gail Gardner, Earl Rogers and Everett Brisindine... contains stories, songs, and poems"...; SWF 89.27/C.3
- Earl Rogers and Ross Knox at Dexter School, Rogers, Earl and Ross Knox, Dexter School; 1 sound cassette, analog; Notes: Performers include: Earl Rogers and Ross Knox... From Acquisitions Inventory, "contains songs, stories, poems and tall tales"...; SWF 89.27/C.4
- [Slim Kite and friends singing and fiddling, tape 1], Kite, Slim (Luther), 1985 March 27; March 27, 1985; 1 sound cassette, analog; NOTES: Performers include: Slim Kite; Marvin Bennett; Bob Cross; Everett Brisindine; John Bradley... From Acquisitions Inventory, "contains songs, recitations, fiddle solos and discussions"...; SWF 89.27/C.5
- [Slim Kite and friends singing and fiddling, tape 2], Kite, Slim (Luther), 1985 March 27; March 27, 1985; 1 sound cassette, analog; NOTES: From Acquisitions Inventory, "contains songs, recitations, fiddle solos and discussions"...; SWF 89.27/C.6
- Tales of Grand Canyon guides in the 30's, tape 1, Kite, Slim (Luther), 1 sound cassette, analog; NOTES: Performers include Slim Kite, Marvin Bennett, and John Bradley... From Acquisitions Inventory, "contains stories about guides taking tourists down the Bright Angel Trail in the 30's; discussions about cowboys; fiddle music and poetry"...; SWF 89.27/C.7
- Tales of Grand Canyon guides in the 30's, tape 2, Kite, Slim (Luther), 1 sound cassette, analog; NOTES: Performers include Slim Kite, Marvin Bennett, and John Bradley... From Acquisitions Inventory, "contains stories about guides taking tourists down the Bright Angel Trail in the 30's; discussions about cowboys; fiddle music and poetry"...; SWF 89.27/C.8
- Grand Canyon Cowboy Band reunion, tape 1, Grand Canyon Cowboy Band, 1 sound cassette, analog; NOTES: Tape includes sides 1 and 4... From Acquisitions Inventory, "Musicians include: Warren Miller; Sam Fenner; Slim Kite; Marvin Bennett; John Bradley... contains rehearsal for concert, cowboy songs, poems, and stories"...; SWF 89.27/C.9
- Grand Canyon Cowboy Band reunion, tape 2, Grand Canyon Cowboy Band, 1 sound cassette, analog; NOTES: Tape includes sides 2 and 5...From Acquisitions Inventory: Individuals recorded are Warren Miller, Sam Fenner, Slim Kite, Marvin Bennett, and John Bradley...Contains rehearsal for concert - cowboy songs, poems, and stories...; SWF 89.27/C.10
- Grand Canyon Cowboy Band reunion, tape 3, Grand Canyon Cowboy Band, 1 sound cassette, analog; NOTES: From Acquisitions Inventory: Individuals recorded are Warren Miller, Sam Fenner, Slim Kite, Marvin Bennett, and John Bradley...Contains rehearsal for concert - cowboy songs, poems, and stories...; SWF 89.27/C.11